<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Juno&#39;s Diary</title>
    <link>http://junosdiary.gihub.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Juno&#39;s Diary</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- 0.132.1</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 22 Mar 2025 22:00:00 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://junosdiary.gihub.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Gradma and Dad&#39;s Wrath</title>
      <link>http://junosdiary.gihub.io/posts/2025-03-22-dads-wrath/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Mar 2025 22:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>http://junosdiary.gihub.io/posts/2025-03-22-dads-wrath/</guid>
      <description>As usual, Grandma wanted a video call with me. I haven&amp;rsquo;t seen Grandma for a while, so I just sat there and staring. Grandma tried so hard asking me to &amp;ldquo;stand up&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;walk around&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;say something&amp;rdquo;&amp;hellip;etc. and that&amp;rsquo;s when Dad blew up, he accused Grandma always being manipulative and trying to control his life. Dad was furious, he threw a lot of f* words around, blamed Grandma for a lot of things that I didn&amp;rsquo;t know.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NC State Vet Medicine Open House</title>
      <link>http://junosdiary.gihub.io/posts/2025-03-08-nc-state-vet-open-house-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Mar 2025 22:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>http://junosdiary.gihub.io/posts/2025-03-08-nc-state-vet-open-house-day/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Awkward day</title>
      <link>http://junosdiary.gihub.io/posts/2025-03-01-this-was-awkward/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Mar 2025 22:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>http://junosdiary.gihub.io/posts/2025-03-01-this-was-awkward/</guid>
      <description>Well, this was an awkward day. I didn&amp;rsquo;t think this small incident would worth its own journal page, but why not.
Just as usual, Dad would give me a bath and leave me alone to play with water for 30 minutes. However, I was having such an amazing time and forgot how long it&amp;rsquo;s been. It must have been hours sitting in that bath tub and still not felt bored.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>You Ruined My World</title>
      <link>http://junosdiary.gihub.io/posts/2025-02-21-you-ruined-my-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 22:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>http://junosdiary.gihub.io/posts/2025-02-21-you-ruined-my-world/</guid>
      <description>I don&amp;rsquo;t know how many times you guys have have ruined my world, I&amp;rsquo;ve lost count, but here they are anyways, because even if you don&amp;rsquo;t remember them, I do !
18 Months Memories Remember those times when I wanted to stay in bath for just two more hours so I can play with my watering can ? For unknown reasons, you just had to drag me out of it, and you keep doing it every day no matter how hard I cried each time !</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dad vs. Mom</title>
      <link>http://junosdiary.gihub.io/posts/2025-02-20-dad-vs-mom/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 22:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>http://junosdiary.gihub.io/posts/2025-02-20-dad-vs-mom/</guid>
      <description>Dad and Mom had a quarrel today. I think it started when Mom accused Dad for working too much, even on weekends, and Dad denied it, as usual, of course. I suppose not everything that Dad does on his computer is considered working, but that&amp;rsquo;s how Mom perceived it anyways.
So for 3 days, Dad had a really long face, pretending there is nothing wrong. When Mom asked &amp;ldquo;Are you OK?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>About Me</title>
      <link>http://junosdiary.gihub.io/aboutme/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Feb 2025 18:58:00 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>http://junosdiary.gihub.io/aboutme/</guid>
      <description>Born in 2023, started writing diary since 1 year old. I like to read and have been reading since 1.
I think I love my dad, at least I kiss him when he asked me to.
I really love my mom, she&amp;rsquo;s always gentle and loves to hug me. She never gets mad at me (at least as of this writing). I always go to her when dad yells at me.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dad Always Overreacts</title>
      <link>http://junosdiary.gihub.io/posts/2025-02-18-dad-always-overreacts/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2025 21:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>http://junosdiary.gihub.io/posts/2025-02-18-dad-always-overreacts/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The First Valentine</title>
      <link>http://junosdiary.gihub.io/posts/2025-02-14-the-first-valentine/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 21:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>http://junosdiary.gihub.io/posts/2025-02-14-the-first-valentine/</guid>
      <description>Today is valentine! Whatever that means. Well, as usual, another date with Declan it is, and to my surprise, my little &amp;ldquo;boyfriend&amp;rdquo; Declan brought me gifts today, is it because of Valentine ? If so, I would like a daily Valentine!
Declan gifted me a small red teddy bear and a book of friendships. Maybe he just wants to be friends more than &amp;ldquo;boyfriend&amp;rdquo;, I am OK with that too.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The first of everything</title>
      <link>http://junosdiary.gihub.io/posts/2024-12-11-the-first-of-everything/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2025 21:58:00 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>http://junosdiary.gihub.io/posts/2024-12-11-the-first-of-everything/</guid>
      <description>There were too many &amp;ldquo;firsts&amp;rdquo;, I can&amp;rsquo;t remember them all, some are fuzzy and some are clear. Either way, I can&amp;rsquo;t verify them, so writing them down is the only way to make sure that I don&amp;rsquo;t lie to whomever is going to interview me when I become famous.
Important Firsts My first words were &amp;ldquo;Dada&amp;rdquo;. (Sure Dad, whatever) Mom taught me to learn how to roll and sit. My first walk happened in Dad&amp;rsquo;s home office (no, he wasn&amp;rsquo;t working, I dare him miss my first baby step) My first kiss was given (or be given, if you know what I mean) to my Dad.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Happy Halloween</title>
      <link>http://junosdiary.gihub.io/posts/2024-11-30-happy-halloween/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Nov 2024 22:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>http://junosdiary.gihub.io/posts/2024-11-30-happy-halloween/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Road Trip to Atlantic Beach</title>
      <link>http://junosdiary.gihub.io/posts/2024-09-10-road-trip-atlantic-beach/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 21:58:00 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>http://junosdiary.gihub.io/posts/2024-09-10-road-trip-atlantic-beach/</guid>
      <description>I honestly think that Dad and Mom were more excited than I am going to the beach. We booked a small room from Airbnb with 1 bedroom and a small kitchen. Somehow I ended up sleeping on the floor, yes, on the floor !! Can you imagine being a baby, sleeping on the cold and hard floor all alone ? It&amp;rsquo;s ridiculous ! So I decided to cry all night, which is how I always get my way and it worked!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I was born</title>
      <link>http://junosdiary.gihub.io/posts/2023-06-07-i-was-born/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 01:43:00 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>http://junosdiary.gihub.io/posts/2023-06-07-i-was-born/</guid>
      <description>This is just a brief introduction to my family. Where I came from, who my mom is, and why I am here
Birth I was born at 1:43 AM on 6/7/2023, weighted 7 pounds and 7 oz after my Mom strugged for 24 hours, allegedly anyways. Technically speaking, I am 20 months now, but I like to sound younger, I mean, who doesn&amp;rsquo;t these days?
At birth, it was supposed to be all sunny and shiny, you know, seeing the lights for the first time and all, but quite the contrary, it was all too dark.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
